雨夜字幕作品
= = = = = = = = = = = =
感受電影魅力
参议员电影
帝门影业公司
帝门影业公司 呈献
黑暗城堡娱乐公司出品
迷雾
改编自斯蒂芬·金同名中篇小说
哇!
Whoa!
所有吃的都得坏掉了
All the food's gonna go bad.
是啊 我列了张清单
Yeah, I drew up a list.
我得尽快去趟商店 免得东西都卖光了
I'll hit the store before it gets all bought out.
妈的
Fuck.
- 还能补救吗? - 不 不行了
- Can you save it? - No. No way.
我得重新再画了
No, I gotta start over from scratch.
等电话恢复了我再联系设计室
I'll call the studio when the phones get back up,
看他们能不能延长我的交稿期限
see if they can extend my deadline.
要不他们还能怎样?
What choice do they have?
别开玩笑了
You kiddin'?
他们在一个下午就能用电脑
They could whip up some bad...
合成出一张烂海报
Photoshop poster in an afternoon.
他们经常这样搞 那帮自大的家伙
They do it all the time. Two big heads.
我昨晚就应该
I should have brought it...
带去地下室的
downstairs with me last night.
就是一个笨 我看
Just stupid, I guess.
嗯 亲爱的 你也不知道
Well, sweetie, you couldn't exactly know that...
那棵树会倒下砸到窗户上
a tree was gonna come flying through the window.
是啊 我还得去趟五金店
Yeah, I'll hit the hardware store too,
买些塑料护板和粘胶布
get some plastic sheeting and duct tape
在天黑前把它给封上
and seal this up before it gets dark, you know.
再订些新玻璃
Order in some new glass.
噢 你知道吗? 那是
Oh, you know what? That was your...
你爷爷的树 是他栽的
that was your grandfather's tree, the one he planted.
我还曾经在那树上玩呢
Used to play in that tree.
只不过是坏了些东西
It's just stuff, though.
你看 咱们都安全 这才是最重要的
You know, we're safe. That's all that counts.
是啊
Yeah.
妈妈 爸爸 你们一定得来看看
Mom, Dad, you gotta come see!
嘿 比利 老实点 行不?
Hey, Billy, take it easy, all right?
我跟你说了别到处乱跑的
I really don't want you running all over the place.
可是你最好来看看
But you gotta come look.
那个小船屋完全砸烂了 烂到家了!
The boathouse is all bashed! Holy crap!
比利
Billy.
抱歉 妈妈 可是你就过来嘛! 快来啊!
Sorry, Mom, but you just gotta come! Come on!
来啊
Come on.
一直跟你说吧 灾难预言家入土了
Having spoken, the Doomsayer departs.
来啊!
Come on!
怎么你们两个老是能逗我笑?
How do you two always manage to make me laugh?
你太容易笑了嘛
You have incredibly low standards.
咱们过去吧 看看毁成什么样了
Let's go, uh, see the damage.
噢 不
No.
- 那是诺顿的树 - 是啊
- Norton's tree. - Yeah.
你指那棵枯树? 那棵树我三年前就
You mean the dead one I've been asking him to take
叫他砍掉的 现在终于被刮倒了
down for three years before it finally blew over?
真的是那棵树?
That tree?
- 真是烂到家了 - 你说的没错
- Really got smooshed. - You ain't kiddin'.
看那边
Look at that.
那是什么 爸爸?
What is it, Daddy?
雾
Mist.
在湖上?
On the lake?
咱们之前也见过湖上的雾
We've had mist on the lake before.
像那样从山上飘下来?
Coming off the mountain like that?
两股气流相交
Two fronts meeting,
风暴的遗留物 诸如此类的
left over from the storm, something like that.
你肯定?
You sure?
宝贝 我可不是气像员
Honey, I'm not the weatherman.
带比利去穿衣服吧
Why don't you take Billy, get him dressed.
我想带他到镇里去
I'll take him to town with me.
好吧 你这是去哪?
Okay. Where you going?
我打算去找咱们的邻居谈谈
I'm gonna go have a little chat...
聊聊他的树
with our neighbor about his tree.
老公
Hon.
别担心 我肯定不会打歪他的鼻梁的
Don't worry, I'm not gonna punch him in the nose.
你知道他会怎么说吗
You know what he's gonna say.
他会说 "告我吧"之类的
He's gonna say, "Sue me," which,
我不知道 或许应该告他
I don't know, maybe we should.
宝贝 跟这家伙发生财产纠纷
Honey, one property dispute with this guy
一次就足以让我郁闷一辈子了
is enough to last me a lifetime.
我就是要问问他保险的事
I'm gonna ask for his insurance information.
好吧
Okay.
- 仅此而已 - 好吧
- That's all. - Yeah.
噢 真他妈的
Ohh! Mother fucker!
啊 妈的
Aw, shit!
噢 去你妈的
Ohh, you mother fucker!
狗娘养的
Cock sucker!
"启动"
"Turn on.
"全缩口"
"Full choke.
"拉动五号...缩口"
Pull five...choke."
我猜你已经看到那...
I guess you've seen the...
船屋
boathouse.
是的 怎样?
Yeah, and...
没什么
Nothin'.
只是想我们应该处理一下保险的事 你说呢?
Just think we should trade insurance info, you know?
就这样
That's all.
噢 我的保险员一定是爱死我了
Oh, my insurance guy's gonna love me.
靠 1980的
Shit. The 1980.
我正打算叫一辆拖车 可是...
I was gonna bring the station wagon, but...
我不知道
I don't know,
从纽约出来的时候天气还好好的
the weather was so beautiful coming out of New York,
我只是...你知道的 大起大落
I just...You know, top down.
真的很抱歉 老兄
I'm sorry, man. I mean it.
真的
Sincerely.
真高兴你这么说
That's nice of you to say.
不 这本来是一辆好车
No, that car was cherry.
我也不想看它那个样子
I hate to see it like that.
好吧 这么跟你说吧
Okay, I'll tell you what,
我会找出我保险员的电话号码
I'll find my insurance guy's number,
迟些给你吧
I'll bring it by later.
- 你看怎么样? - 没问题
- That okay? - No problem.
还有 戴维...
So, uh, David...
你今天准备
you're not heading into town...
到镇上去 对吧?
today by any chance, are you?
德雷顿家
连CMP都出动了
Well, CMP's out in force.
或许我们很快就会有电了
Maybe we'll get our power back.
这场暴风雨不小
I know. Some storm, huh?
还真没见过
One for the books, yeah.
有那么几分钟 就在昨晚
For a moment there last night,
我以为我们要玩完了得回老家了
I thought we were gonna take off and head for Oz.
WZON电台已经停播
WZON is off the air,
不过波特兰台还在播放
but Portland's still broadcasting.
爸爸 快看
Daddy, look.
这些都是基地里的人
Guys from the base.
从山上来的?
From up the mountain?
那个箭头计划?
The Arrowhead Project?
对了 你是本地人
Well, you're a local.
知道他们在上面干嘛吗?
Any idea what they do up there?
导弹防御研究
Missile defense research.
我想你肯定也听过这些事
You know, I'm sure you've heard the stories.
嗯 当然了
Oh, sure.
洗衣店的那个女的常说的 嗯
The woman at the Laundromat says that, uh,
他们发现一架坠毁的飞碟
they have a crashed flying saucer up...
里面还有冻僵了的外星人遗体
there with frozen alien bodies.
对 就是埃德娜说的 没错
Right. Miss Edna. Yeah.
她可是小道消息小姐
Miss Tabloid.
"我有个大脚婴儿" (引自《地狱男爵》)
"I Had Bigfoot's Baby."
"撒旦的脸映在了油井的火中" (引自《地狱男爵》)
"Satan's Face Appears in Oil Well Fire."
你知道 那些可都是"可靠"消息
You know, real reliable stuff.
噢 他们还挺急的
Well, they're in a hurry.
没准他们也断电了
Maybe their power's out too.
啊 还是没信号
Huh. Still no signal.
你先去吧
Why don't you go ahead?
我去那边的付费电话给史蒂夫打个电话
I'm gonna try Steph on a pay phone.
我可以跟诺顿先生一起吗 爸爸?
Can I go with Mr. Norton, Daddy?
可以 如果你答应牵住他的手的话
Sure, if you promise to hold his hand, I guess.
- 好的 - 好
- Yeah. - Yeah.
这张是清单
Here's a list.
- 好的 - 好吧?
- Sure. - Okay?
店里见
Meet you guys in there.
牵住手
Hold hands.
不好意思 我不知道他是你妹妹
I'm sorry. I didn't know it was your sister.
那东西看起来真够怪的
That looks so freaky!
- 萨利 嗨 - 嗨 德雷顿先生
- Sally, hey. - Hey, Mr. Drayton.
你们看起来忙坏了
You guys look jammed up.
是啊 一半的人没来
Yeah, well, half the staff didn't show,
而且电也断了
plus the power's out.
噢 不 怎么 没有后备发电机?
Oh, no. What, no backup generator?
只能用来给食物保鲜
Only to keep the food cold.
其他的么 欢迎来到黑暗时代
Everything else, welcome to the Dark Ages,
别忘了带钱包
and bring your checkbook.
嘿 星期四晚 史蒂夫和我想聚一聚
Hey, Thursday night, Steph and I want a date night.
- 帮忙看小孩? - 嗯哼 我会去啦
- Baby-sit? - Heck, yeah. I'm there.
噢 我的天
Oh, my God.
都是因为暴风雨
The storm.
每个人都想着积点货
Everybody's stockin' up.
我们一开门就这么忙了
Been like this since we opened.
倒霉的一天 哼?
Crappy day, huh?
嗯 今早个个脾气都不小
Eh, everyone's a little pissed off this morning.
早啊 卡莫迪太太
Morning, Mrs. Carmody.
有这么多人排队 真不知道这是好还是坏
With lines like these, I don't know how good it is,
不过 先这么凑合着吧
but I guess we'll have to make do.
- 埋头苦干吧 伙计 - 我就知道
- Keep your head down, pal. - I know it.
嘿 小冠军
Hey, champ.
你妻子应该当医生
Your wife should be a doctor.
就凭她这手字
She could make a fortune in Manhattan...
在曼哈顿肯定可以发大财
with this handwriting.
是啊 得常看才能懂
Yeah, it takes some getting used to.
你去买你的东西吧
Why don't you get your stuff?
我在收银处等你
I'll meet you at the checkout.
好吧 就这样
Okay, done.
嘿 戴维 谢谢你今天载我出来
Hey, David, thanks for helping me out today.
你是不是跟诺顿先生要成为朋友了 爸爸?
Are you and Mr. Norton gonna be friends now, Daddy?
噢 我也说不准
Oh, I don't know.
"朋友"似乎有还些谈不上
"Friends" might be stretching it a little.
我想你们不再生对方的气了
I guess you're not mad at each other anymore.
我想也是
I guess not.
那这应该算个开始 哼?
And that's a start, huh?
抱歉 夫人 记数器不能用了
I'm sorry, ma'am, the registers are down.
备用电源也快用完了
The power outage got us too.
希望我们尽快能恢复供电
Hopefully we'll have power up pretty soon.
巴士会在30钟后离开
The bus leaves in 30 minutes.
我们能赶上 放心吧?
We'll make it, okay?
你们去选糖果 我在这里排队等
You guys get the goodies. I'll wait in line.
我需要些零钱 在5号口
I need some change on register five.
早上好 瑞普拉女士
Good morning, Ms. Reppler.
你好 瑞普拉奶奶
Hello, Ms. Reppler.
啊 你也好 比利·德雷顿
Well, hello to you, Billy Drayton.
昨晚怎么样?
How'd you hold up in the storm?
昨晚有棵树砸到了
We had a tree come through the picture...
落地窗上 那正好是我的画室
window last night, right in my studio.
还有那个船屋也被砸烂了
And the boathouse got all smooshed.
诺顿先生的树倒在了上面
Mr. Norton's tree fell on it.
哎唷
Ouch.
- 是啊 - 很遗憾发生那种事
- Yeah. - Sorry to hear that.
你们怎么样?
How'd you guys make out?
噢 我们还好 这几份清单才是个事呢
Oh, we're fine. It's the listings I'm worried about.
不过最起码 我敢打赌
At the very least, I'll bet every one of...
每个"待售"的牌子都倒了
our "For Sale" signs fell over.
我们学校也受灾了 你还不知道?
We had damage at the school, wouldn't you know?
就是因为没有修屋顶
That's what we get for not fixing...
才会落得这样
that roof when we should've,
可是我们的资金每年都在削减...
but with funds being cut every year...
你以为儿童教育
You'd think educating children
应该是国家的头等事
would be more of a priority in this country,
可是你错了
but you'd be wrong.
政府有更好的事去挥霍纳税人的钱
Government's got better things to spend our money on,
例如给大公司注资 还有做炸弹
like corporate handouts and building bombs.
爸爸 外面着火了吗? 妈妈没事吧?
Daddy, is there a fire? Is Mommy all right?
我肯定她没事 别担心
I'm sure she's fine. Don't worry, okay?
专心做你的事 萨利
Mind what you're doing, Sally.
噢 拜托 我们有10天假
Oh, come on, we got 10 days' leave.
给你看假条
Check our papers.
听着 我说了 所有假期都已取消
Look, I told you, all leaves are cancelled.
我也不知为何
I don't know why.
我得过那边药店去看看
I gotta go check the pharmacy out.
你们三个五分钟后到吉普车那见我
Three men meet me back at the Jeep in five minutes.
这是命令
That's an order.
妈的 老兄! 再过半小时
Shit, man! Another half an hour,
我们就得走了
and we'd have been gone.
噢 我的天
Oh, my God!
雾里面有东西
Something in the mist!
雾里面有东西...
Something in the mist...
已经拖走约翰·李了!
took John Lee!
丹 先缓口气
Dan, catch your breath.
雾里面有个东西拖走了约翰·李
Something in the mist took John Lee.
我能听见他的惨叫
I could hear him screaming.
关上门! 关上门! 我的天哪!
Shut the doors! Shut the doors! My God!
爸爸 我害怕 咱们回家好吗?
Daddy, I'm scared. Can we go home?
别出到外面去
Don't go out there.
雾里面有东西 它拖走约翰·李了
There's something in the mist. It took John Lee.
别扯淡了! 我要回我车里去
Screw that! I'm gettin' in my car.
先生 不要!
Mister, no!
抱紧我 爸爸
Please hold me.
没事的 没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
一定是污染的雾 许多工厂都在拉姆福德那里
It's a pollution cloud. The mills down in Rumford.
化学剂爆炸之类的 肯定是
Some kind of chemical explosion. Has to be.
发生什么了?
What is it?
到底怎么了?
What's going on?
是死神
It's death.
蹲下!
Stay down!
爸爸!
Daddy!
你没事吧?
You okay?
应该是地震
That was an earthquake.
我跟你说 是那些该死的工厂爆炸了!
I tell you, the goddamn mills blew up!
大家都没事吗? 有人受伤吗?
Is everyone okay? Is anyone hurt?
每个都待着别动 好吧?
Everybody just stay put, okay?
呆在店里别出去
Just stay inside the store.
不行 我不能呆在这
I can't. I can't stay here.
我得回家看我的孩子
I gotta get home to my kids.
别 别 别出去
No. No, don't go out there.
死神就在外面 这是世界末日
It's death out there. It's the end of days.
别说了 行吗? 别说了
Stop it, okay? Stop it.
好了 大家 大家都放松点 好吗?
Please, everybody, everybody just relax, okay?
他说的对 咱们得保持冷静
He's right. Let's just stay cool.
咱们先来分析分析到底发生了什么
Let's just try to figure out what happened.
对不起 我...我不能就这样呆在这
I'm sorry, I...I can't just stay here.
我得回家找我的孩子
I have to get home to my kids.
夫人 不要 你千万不能出去
Ma'am, no, you can't go out there.
可能是有毒的云雾
Could be a poisonous gas cloud.
你没听见那个男的惨叫吗?
Didn't you hear that man screaming?
我同意 咱们最好待在这直到把事情缕清
I agree. Let's stay here until we figure it out.
你们都没听我说么!
WO You're not listening!
我不能呆在这
I can't stay here.
旺达正在照看小维克托 她只有8岁
Wanda's looking after little Victor. She's only 8.
有时候她甚至忘了
Sometimes she forgets...
她应该照看他
she's supposed to be watching him.
我跟他们说我只是出来几分钟而已
I told them I'd only be gone a few minutes.
她只有8岁
She's only 8.
为了他们
For their sakes,
不要去
don't.
难道没人愿意帮帮我吗?
Well, isn't anybody gonna help me?
嘘 没事的 孩子
Shh. It's okay, pal.
没人愿意送一位女士回家吗?
Won't somebody here see a lady home?
你吗?
You?
你?
- 没事的 孩子 - 你?
- It's okay, buddy. - You?
夫人 别这样 我自己还有孩子呢
Ma'am, please, I got my own boy to worry about.
我希望你们都下地狱
I hope you all rot in hell.
夫人 求你了 等到...
Ma'am, please, wait until...
好了 咱们得开始打扫一下了 好不?
Okay, let's start cleaning up, okay?
收拾一下那些碎瓶子
Get the spilled bottles,
烂玻璃 诸如此类的东西
broken glass, stuff like that.
第三过道有医药用品
Aisle three has medical supplies.
没事的 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
好了 放松 小冠军 坚强点
All right, easy, champ. Come on.
坚强点
Come on.
坚强点 好了
Come on. All right, hey, hey, hey.
可不能一直这样哭哦 儿子
Can't keep crying like this, pal.
坚强些
Come on!
坚强些 你会伤到你自己的
Come on, you're gonna hurt yourself.
- 坚强些 你没事的 - 我想要妈妈
- Come on, are you all right? - I want Mommy!
好了 我知道你想妈妈
All right, I know you want Mommy.
好了 尽量试着深呼吸
All right, just try to breathe.
试着深呼吸
Just try to breathe, okay?
试着深呼吸 孩子 没事的
Just try to breathe, pal. That's okay.
没事了
It's all right.
我很久没见他这样吸拇指了
I haven't seen him suck his thumb like...
上一次是在他2岁时
this since he was 2 years old.
他受了惊吓
He's in shock.
我想我们都是
I think we all are.
你们没见过吧
You haven't met.
阿曼达·旦芙蕾
Amanda Dunfrey.
她是新来的 这个学期才过来
She's new in town as of this semester.
教三年级
Teaches third grade
还那些特殊的孩子 因为莫歇尔退休了
and the special ed kids, now that Mosher's retired.
她很棒 孩子们都喜欢她
She's wonderful. The kids love her.
而戴维是名艺术家
And David's an artist.
他做电影海报之类的
He does movie posters and such.
而我...
And me...
上帝 我又乱侃了
Lord, I'm babbling away like...
就像个派对上的老女人
some old biddy at a tea party!
我想我有些语无伦次了
My nerves are jangled, I guess.
小孩安静下来了?
Boy settle down?
他怎么样?
How is he?
还有点烧
Still hot.
我帮他拿点阿斯匹林吧
Why don't I get him some aspirin.
- 第三过道 - 好的
- Aisle three. - Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
丹怎么样了?
How's Dan?
他的鼻子已经止血了
His nose stopped bleedin'.
他平静多了 有人给了他一剂安定
He's calmer now. Somebody gave him a Valium.
真不敢相信他怎样跑进来的
Can't believe the way he ran in here.
从来没见过他那样
Never seen him like that.
我得找个东西给我的孩子盖上
I need something to cover my boy up.
有毯子吗?
Got any blankets?
家居垫 在储物仓
Furniture pads. Loadin' dock.
我还得继续检查其他人
Gonna keep checkin' on people.
如果有需要 尽管喊我
If you need anything, just holler.
当然了 萨利 能帮把手吗?
You bet. Sally, you mind?
噢 我很想帮忙 可是我必须得帮他打扫这里
Oh, I'd love to. I really should help him clean up.
- 我来看着他吧 - 好的
- I'll take him. - Okay.
爸爸 别走
Daddy, don't go.
不走 我就去一会儿 乖比利
No, I'll be gone two seconds, Big Bill.
来 我去帮你拿毯子
Come on, I'm gonna get your blanket.
瑞普拉奶奶在这
Mrs. Reppler's here,
而且还有土尔曼太太
and so is Mrs. Turman.
我就在附近 好吗?
I'll be close by, okay?
- 好吧 - 别担心 我不走远 好吗?
- Okay. - Don't worry, I'm not far. Okay?
让我看看你
Let me look at you.
想躺下来吗?
Wanna lie down?
嗯
Yeah.
好了
There you go.
一旦它被吹散
Soon as it blows away,
我们就可以平安自由地出去了
we can walk out of here safe and free,
但是我们不能太大意
but we have to be smart about it.
第一个我们要做的 就是要保持头脑清醒
First thing we need to do is keep our wits about us
然后再查出发生了什么事
and find out what's happened.
那我们怎么办 老兄?
Well, Howe gonna do that, my man?
我们这里手机没信号 也没有无线电
We've got no phone signal, got no radio.
我相信他们正在处理
I'm sure they're working on...
我们说的这些问题
those problems as we speak.
我们有理由相信 恢复通讯正常
It stands to reason that restoring communications
是他们的首要任务
would be their top priority.
天哪
Jeez!
噢 妈的
Oh, shit.
妈的
Shit!
真见鬼
God damn it!
婊子
Bitch!
很明显我们...
It's obvious that we're...
我们遇到了某种自然灾害
we're in some kind of natural disaster here.
我就看不出这他妈的
Ain't nothin' obvious about this...
有什么明显
sombitch from where I sit.
依我看 也不是什么自然性的灾祸
There ain't nothin' natural about it either.
说的对
That's right.
这是审判日 它最终还是来了
It's Judgment Day, and it's come round at last.
没什么比这更明显更自然的了
There is nothing more obvious or natural than that.
噢 完了 这回
Ohh, fuck, now.
是你们自己种下的祸种
You've done that to yourself,
只因你们一生作孽
by a life of sin and dissolution.
嘿 哇! 戴维!
Hey, whoa! David!
嗯 你们听到动静了吗?
Hey, you guys hear that?
发电机? 我们正准备去检查一下呢
The generator? We're just gonna check it out.
不 不 我关了发电机了
No, no, I turned the generator off.
它...它正储电呢
It...it was backing up.
没...没人听见那声音?
N...nobody else heard that sound?
什么声音?
What sound?
我不知道 似乎很诡异的响声
I don't know, like a...weird noise,
在黑暗里面
back there in the dark.
就像有东西 正挤压着门
Like something was, like pressing against the door.
你听见那声音是在
Did you hear it before the lights...
关灯之前 还是之后?
went out, or after?
不 是之后
No, only after.
之后 不过 听着 我听见了 好不?
After, but, look, I heard it, okay?
没人在说你撒谎
Nobody's calling you a liar.
可听起来就是那意思
That's what it sounds like.
别扯那么远 德雷顿先生
No, no. Now, don't be thattaway, Mr. Drayton.
毫无疑问 你是被吓着了
You had a scare, no doubt.
要不我们都下去检查一下?
What say we all go check it out?
给
Here.
天
Man.
这里可真够臭的
It's pretty rank in here.
- 麦伦 过去看看 - 好的
- go check it out. - All right.
继续 启动开关
Go on, fire it up.
好了!
All right!
关掉它吧
Shut it off!
哇噢 真臭啊!
Holy crow, don't that stink!
外面有东西
Something's got the exhaust vent...
把排气孔给堵上了
plugged up from the outside.
你确定它有足够的电
You get it running long enough...
把门拉开点吗?
to raise that door a little,
我出去把堵着的东西清理掉
I'll go out and clear whatever's blockin' it.
不 不 你不能那样做
No, no, you can't do that.
为什么不? 那是道电动门 对吧?
Why not? It's an electric door, right?
嗯 是的 可是让他出去
Well, yeah, but it may not be wise...
可能不太明智
to send him out there.
好吧 那我来做
Okay, I'll do it.
不 听着 这不是谁出去的事
No, look, it's not about who goes out there.
怎么 你以为我做不来?
What, don't you think I can do it?
嘿! 我去! 那是我的主意!
Hey! I want to go! It was my idea.
啊 等等 先别动 行不?
Well, wait, just stop, okay?
吉...吉姆 对吗?
J...Jim, right?
麦伦? 你们都...
You guys are...
你们 你们看来还没弄明白
you, well, you don't seem to understand,
或者是你们努力不去理解
or you're tryin' real hard not to.
这不是什么普通的雾 好不?
This is no ordinary mist, okay?
你要是开了那门 就会有什么东西进来了
You open that door, and something gets in here.
比如什么?
Like what?
嗯 什么都可能 我是说 能弄出我听到的那种声音的东西
Well, like whatever, I mean, made that noise I heard.
我说你们是不是故意装傻?
Are you guys being willfully dense?
德雷顿先生 你得原谅我
Mr. Drayton, you'll pardon me,
但是我不信你听见什么声音
but I'm not convinced that you heard anything.
我是说 我们现在什么也没听见 对吧?
I mean, we're not hearing anything now, right?
有人听见吗?
Anybody?
看?
See?
我知道 我知道你是个了不起的画家
Now, I know, I know...you're a big shot artist
在纽约和好莱坞
with connections in New York...
以及类似的地方都有关系
and Hollywood and all like that,
不过那并不能让你比别人强
but that don't make you better...
至少对我来说不是
than anybody else, not in my book.
嘿 我没那么说
Hey, I didn't say that.
我也不喜欢被所谓的大学生
Nor do I like being talked down to or called stupid
贬低或称为笨蛋
by a guy who went to college,
仅仅因为他有些神经过敏
just 'cause he's got the jitters.
伙计们 即使没有发电机也没什么
Fellas, it doesn't even matter about the generator.
没有它食物一样可以保存
The food'll keep without it.
小子 我来发动电机 你抬起门
Kid, I'm gonna start the motor, you raise the door,
当你有足够的空间的时候 就喊一声
and you yell out when you got enough room.
好 好的 很好
Yeah. Okay, good.
等等
Wait.
这简直...
This is...
你们为了一台无关紧要的发电机
You guys gonna let this kid risk his life
居然让这孩子拿他的生命去冒险?
over a generator that doesn't even matter?
你就不能他妈的闭嘴?
Would you just shut the fuck up already?
诺姆!
Norm!
听着 德雷顿先生 我跟你说
kListen, Mr. Drayton, I tell you what.
如果下次你有什么想要发表的
The next time you got somethin' to say,
先称称自己有多少斤两
you count your teeth,
因为我对你的废话恶心的要死
because I'm sick to death of your bullshit.
明白不?
All right?
来吧 麦伦
Come on.
- 这是疯了! - 随他们去吧
- This is crazy! - Leave 'em be.
我成什么了 诋毁他们的人格还是什么?
What am I, impugning their manhood or something?
听我说 他们已经失去平衡意识了
Listen, they've lost their sense of proportion.
这到底是怎么了?
What's going on here?
在外面超市里
Out there in the market,
他们被吓到了 彷徨了
they were scared and confused.
而在这 有他们能解决的问题
In here, there's a problem they can solve,
于是他们拼死也要解决它
so they're goddamn gonna solve it.
- 准备好了 孩子? - 开始吧
- Ready, kid? - Let's rock.
诺姆 拜托
Norm, come on.
不要 兄弟
Don't, man.
这是个错误
It's a mistake.
胆小鬼
Pussy.
停
Hold up!
那么...
So...
有怪物么?
any boogeymen?
真的挺吓人 是不是 诺姆?
Pretty scary, ain't it, Norm?
是呀 没错
Yeah, right.
诺姆
Norm.
诺姆!
Norm!
他妈的什么东西?
What the fuck!
弄掉它! 弄掉它!
Ahh! Get it off! Get it off!
把这个变态的东西弄掉!
Get this friggin' thing off me!
把它弄掉! 救我!
Get it off! Help me!
救我! 救我!
Help me! Help me!
上帝!
Jesus!
那还有! 那还有!
There's more! There's more!
来人帮把手啊!
Somebody help me.
都他妈的在等什么呢?
What the fuck are you waitin' for?
挺住!
Hang on!
抓紧他! 抓紧他!
Hold him still! Hold him still!
噢 天啊!
Oh, Jesus!
妈的 噢 妈的!
Shit! Oh, shit!
噢 妈的!
Oh, shit!
戴维 情况不妙啊!
David, it's no good!
打开发电机!
Start the generator.
嘿 对不起
Hey, I'm sorry.
我是说 我怎么...
I mean, how the...
我怎么知道你到底指什么?
how the hell was I supposed to know what you meant?
你说你听到了什么
You said you heard something.
我怎么知道你到底指什么?
How was I supposed to know what you meant?
你应该说的更明白一点
You should've said what you meant better.
我不知道
I don't know,
我以为不过是只大鸟或什么的
I thought maybe it was a big bird or something.
是你害死了那个孩子!
You got that kid killed!
你有好好看过外面吗? 哼?
Did you get a good look at it? Huh?
你有好好想想你的所作所为吗?
Did you get a good look at what you did?
- 哼? - 戴维!
- Huh? - David!
别再打他了! 解决不了问题的!
Don't hit him anymore! Doesn't solve anything!
你们两个混蛋 是你们害死他的!
You two assholes, you got that kid killed!
而我却他妈的溅了一身血!
And I got his fuckin' blood on me!
好了 我没事了
Okay, I'm done.
好了
Okay.
接下来怎么办?
What's next?
关掉发电机
Kill the generator.
那是首要的
That's the first thing.
对不起
I'm sorry.
噢 我的天!
Jesus Christ! Oh, God!
很...很抱歉 那个孩子...
I'm...I'm sorry about the kid.
噢 天哪...
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
我们得离开这儿
We oughta get out of here.
嗯 我们可没有强迫他
Hey, we didn't twist his arm.
没错 他就是个傻孩子
Yeah,he's a fuckin' kid.He's supposed to be stupid.
你还有什么借口 哼?
What's your excuse, huh?
滚出去
Get outta here.
回超市里去 守在门口
Go back in the market. Stay by the door.
什么也别说 对谁都别说
Don't say anything, to anybody.
现在还不行
Not yet.
现在不行
妈的
Shit.
戴维? 有灯吗?
David? Need a little light here.
我们必须得告诉他们
We have to tell 'em.
那些在超市里的人
The people in the market,
我们不能让他们再走出去了
we have to stop 'em going outside.
他们不会相信咱们的
They won't believe us.
不信也得信
They have to.
刚才的事情 我自己都不确定
I'm not sure I believe it. I was here.
我们见的东西根本难以想象
W...what we saw was impossible.
你知道的 不是吗?
You know that, don't you?
我是说 应该...
I mean, what...
我们应该说什么?
what do we say?
怎么才能让他们相信?
How do we convince them?
奥利 那些该死的触腕
Ollie, what the hell were...
到底是长在什么上的?
those tentacles even attached to?
噢 我的天! 你 你没事吧?
Oh, my God! Are...are you all right?
嘘!没事没事 这不是我的血 我没事
Shh! Yeah, yeah, it's not my blood. I'm fine.
到底发生什么了?
W...what the hell happened?
我会解释的 等一会 行不?
I'll explain. Give me a minute, okay?
我得先处理一些事
I need to deal with something first.
拜托了 我必须得...
Please, I've got to...
我不能让比利看到我这样
I can't let Billy see me like this.
他已经够怕的了
He's scared enough.
就给我一分钟 分散他的注意力 好吗?
Just give me a minute. Keep him distracted. Okay?
好的
Okay.
嘿 关于诺姆的事我很抱歉
Hey, look, I'm sorry about Norm.
我也是
Me too.
我是说 我不是辩解什么 只是表达歉意
I mean, I ain't makin' excuses, I'm just sayin'.
听着 我们得告诉人们
Look, we need to tell people.
没必要讲它怎么发生的
No need to say how it went down...
或者类似的细节
or anything like that,
不过 我们处境危险
but, uh, we're in the deep shit here.
人们有必要知道
People need to know.
那些外镇人怎么办?
What about the out-of-towners?
他们很多人也困在店里了
We got plenty of them in the store.
我们从谁那里开始呢?
Where do we even start?
- 布伦特·诺顿? - 那个快嘴?
- Brent Norton? - That windbag?
他可是纽约重量级的大律师
He's an important attorney in New York.
那家伙有可能坐上法官椅的
That fellow could be on the bench one day.
这对本镇和外镇的人都很有用
Counts a lot with people of this town, or anywhere.
- 是啊 说的对 - 得快点 戴维
- Yeah, that's right. - Do it quick, David.
我们还得研究一下如何阻止
We've got to discuss how we're gonna stop...
那鬼东西进来店里
that thing getting in here.
等 等一下 你说"进来"是什么意思
W...wait. What do you mean getting in?
你关了库房门
You shut the loading door.
是的 可是整个店的正面
Yeah, but the entire front of...
都是玻璃板的
the store is plate glass.
噢 我的天呀
Jesus Christ.
我正想你去哪了呢
I was wondering where you'd gotten to.
嗯 听着...
Um, listen...
那个人慌慌张张的进来
that guy that came in here,
鼻子流着血的人
the one with the bloody nose...
他们...他们...我们见着大触腕了
they're...they're...We saw tentacles.
进展不顺利 是不?
Ain't goin' very well, is it?
- 你...什么? - 来这边 你最好来...
- You...what? - Come here, you've got...
来这边
Come here.
告诉他
Tell him.
是真的
It's true.
大触腕 没错
Tentacles. Yeah.
呃 先生们 呃...
Um, gentlemen, um...
不好意思 我...我想我没那么笨
I'm sorry, I...I'm just not that stupid.
我是说 你们以为我是什么?
I mean, what do you take me for?
我被吓着了
I'm shocked.
我被吓着了 这事儿真的很没品
I'm shocked. It's pretty tasteless
利用刚刚发生的一切
using what's happening here to...
想让我看起来像个白痴
try to make me look like an idiot.
不 不 事情不是你想的那样
No, no, that's not what's going on here.
听着 跟我回储物仓看下 怎样?
Look, come back to the loading dock, okay?
我会指给你看
I'll show you.
血 一大块触腕就在...在地板上
Blood. A chunk of tentacle on...on the floor.
不
No.
不? 你这什么意思?
No? What do you mean no?
不 我们还有真正要紧的事要处理
No. We've got real problems to deal with here,
而这个可怜的玩笑
and this pathetic attempt at a joke
已经开到头了
has gone far enough.
诺顿先生 要什么理由才能让我们...
Mr. Norton, what reason could we possibly have...?
噢 拜托! 拜托!
Oh, please! Please!
这是针对去年
This is payback for the lawsuit that...
我对他提起诉讼的报复
I filed against him last year,
而你们几个都在帮着他
and you guys are backing him up.
觉得赢的还不够 哼?
So winning wasn't enough, huh?
如果你想加倍羞辱我
You wanted to humiliate me some more,
弄条橡皮蛇来 当着这些...这些乡巴佬
show me a rubber snake while these...these hicks
让他们围着我笑到翻才行
stand around laughing their asses off.
小心你在叫谁乡巴佬!
Watch who you callin' a hick!
- 嘿 嘿 你妈的...! - 诺顿先生...
- Hey, hey, fuck...! - Mr. Norton...
我发誓 你把我们都怪错了
I swear, you have got us all wrong.
你做的还不算过份
You're not too crazy about, um,
对外来人 不是吗?
out-of-towners, are you?
我只是在这花花钱 上上税
I only spend my money, and I pay my taxes here,
而我却发现你在我背后说我坏话
and I have seen you talking behind my back.
原来你们是一块的
Y'all stick together.
我觉得自己很蠢
Well, don't I feel foolish?
今天我真的以为你对我很友好
I actually thought you were being kind to me today,
还有 嗯 得谢谢你搭我出来
and, well, thanks for setting me straight.
而且我真高兴那棵树
And I'm glad that tree fell on...
砸到你的船屋上
your boathouse, you know that?
高兴 砸的太漂亮了
Glad. Smashed it in pretty good,
不是吗? 爽极了
didn't it? Fantastic.
现在 你们每个人 都离我远点
Now, all of y'all, just stay out of my way.
我知道你吓坏了 老兄 我也吓坏了
I know you're scared, man. I'm scared too.
- 大家的生命都岌岌可危 - 戴维...
- Lives are at stake around here. - David...
好吧 我儿子的生命 现在 我需要你
Okay, my son's life. Now, I need you.
布伦特 拜托了 别这么死脑瓜骨行不
Brent, please, get your head out of your ass.
好吧 我会硬拖你过去的 如果有必要的话
All right, I'll drag you back there if I have to.
过来这边
Come here.
戴维 把你那臭爪子拿开
David, get your goddamn hands off of me!
小心我再控告你
I'll sue your ass again!
控告你 而这次你肯定会进监狱!
Sue your ass, and this time you'll go to jail!
这个人打了我
This man assaulted me.
他打了我 你们都可以做证
He assaulted me. You were witness to it.
这人简直疯了 他疯了
This man's crazy. He's crazy.
没有
No.
他没疯 我真希望他疯了 可他没有
He isn't. I wish he was, but he isn't.
店里的每个人 你们想过来这里看看吗?
Everyone in the store, you want to come back here?
有件事你们得听听
There's something you need to hear.
与大家息息相关
It concerns you all.
行了吧
Okay.
等等 我不知道你们这些人
Wait. I don't know what...
到底在干什么
you people think you're doing.
你喝多了?
You're drinking?
看在主的份上 奥利
For Christ's sake, Ollie.
你想让我打你的报告吗?
Do you want me to report you?
你不想要你工作了?
You want to lose your job?
听着 我现在要开始记名了
Look, I'm gonna be taking down names,
就从你开始
starting with you.
还有我已经打算报一份给警察了
And I am prepared to file a police report.
- 好极了 伯德 你就记你的名吧 - 我会的
- Fine, Bud, write down your names. - I will.
不过与此同时 你就闭上嘴仔细听着
But in the meantime, shut the fuck up and listen.
这位是戴维·德雷顿先生
This is Mr. David Drayton.
你们得听听他要说些什么
You need to hear what he's got to say...
如果你们打算离开的话
if you're thinking about leaving.
去姐姐那边 好吗?
...go hang out with the ladies, all right?
听着 别害怕
Listen, don't be scared.
没事的
It's okay.
好了
Okay.
事情是这样的
This is how it is.
现在 我也不知道这雾到底是什么...
Now, I don't know what this mist is...
不过有东西在里面
but there are things in it,
而且很危险 就如丹所说的
and they're dangerous, like Dan said.
没错
That's right.
就是这样
That's exactly right.
什么样的东西?
What kind of things?
我从没见过 这事发生得太快了
I never saw it. It happened too fast.
我被击倒了
I got knocked down.
我们有五个人去了储物仓
Five of us went back in the loading dock.
其中包括吉姆 麦伦 奥利...
It was Jim, Mellon, Ollie...
我...
me...
诺姆 那个搬运男孩
Norm, the bag boy.
- 我们打开了吊门...- 怎么不见诺姆?
- We opened the door...- Where's Norm?
这样诺姆就能出去外面
so Norm could go out and...
清理发电机的通风口
clear the vent for the generator.
有东西从雾里伸了出来并拖走了他
Something come out of the mist and took him.
拖走他?
Took him?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
就是说...弄死了他
Just...killed him.
我是说硬拽死的
I mean dragged him off.
现在 朋友们 我不知道这些是什么东西
Now, guys, I don't know what these things are.
我们见到的只有一些触腕
All we saw were tentacles.
触腕 他说的
Tentacles, he says.
触腕 来自X行星的
Tentacles from Planet X.
那是骗人的 知道吧
It's a lie, you know.
我是说 这些人
I mean, all these people...
就是合伙骗人的
do is just lie each other up.
那是一堆狗屎
It's a pile of shit.
当然是骗人的 当然是骗人的
Of course it's a lie. Of course it's a lie.
简直神经质
It's lunacy.
表面看起来
From the look of it,
那些触腕是从啤酒罐钻出来的
the tentacles are coming out of the beer cans.
好吧 伯德 别曲解我们的话
All right, uh, Bud, don't take our word for it.
去看看
Go look.
就在那里
Over there.
这是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
看起来 可能我们...
It appears we may have a problem...
的麻烦来大了
of some magnitude here.
对 把他们都排成行 谢谢
Yeah, just keep 'em in line. Thanks.
让我...
Let me...
来拯救这些人吧
help these people.
让我...
Let me...
让我来宣扬您的真理吧
let me preach your word.
让我来眩耀您的圣光吧
Let me shine your light,
因为他们不全是坏人
'cause they're not all bad.
他们不可能全是坏人
They can't all be bad.
有些人是可以挽救的 不是吗?
Some can be saved, can't they?
是的
Yes.
有些人可以带去...
Some can be brought...
天堂的神圣之门 通过您的恩惠
to heaven's holy gates through your grace.
我确信如此
I have to believe that,
虽然我知道大多数
though I know most will swim...
都将在火湖中永世煎熬
in the lake of fire forever.
如果我能挽救那么几个...
If I can save a few...
即使一个...
even one...
那样我也算不枉此生了
then my life will have counted for something.
我一定会竭尽全力
I will have pulled my weight.
我一定会为您效忠
I will have earned my place at your side.
我一定会求仁得仁 死得其所
I will have served a purpose here on this earth.
有人吗?
Hello?
什么事?
What?
我只是想用一下洗手间
I just need to use the bathroom.
好的 那么 给你用吧
Okay. Well, then, have at it.
夫人...
Ma'am...
我...我只想跟你说 那没什么的
I...I just want you to know that it's okay...
我是说...被吓到
being scared, I mean...
还有 如果你需要朋友的话...
and, well, if you need a friend...
你知道 找个人聊聊
you know, someone to talk to.
我有朋友了...
I have a friend...
天上的主 我每天都同他谈心
God up above. I talk to him every day.
别装做你高我一等
Don't you condescend to me.
您说什么?
I'm sorry?
永远别想 你挖苦不了我
Not ever. You don't mock me.
我不是那个意思
That's not what I was doing.
噢 那我来告诉你吧...
Well, I'll tell you what...
当我需要个像你这样的朋友的时候
the day I need a friend like you,
我只需要轻轻的蹲下
I'll just have myself a little squat...
拉堆屎就行了
and shit one out.
或许你真的相信这个
Maybe you do believe this.
或许那些都不是骗人的 是幻觉 不管什么
Maybe they're not lies, they're delusions. Whatever.
就现有的情况来看 证据是明显不足的
Uh, the fact remains, the evidence here is flimsy.
这都是愚蠢的做法
It's bordering on ludicrous.
嘿 这里不是法庭
Hey, this isn't a courtroom.
你也不是在为案子做辩护
You're not arguing a case,
你这么做帮不上忙
and you're doing nothing but damage,
只会添麻烦
talking the way you are.
而你大可搞一大堆牛血
And you can throw as much cow's blood...
洒到储物间 多少都行
around the loading dock as you want to.
还是没有人会上你的当的
You still haven't fooled anyone.
别理他了 戴维
Leave it alone, David.
你没法说服人们有地方着了火
You can't convince some people there's a fire
即使他们头发都烧起来了
even when their hair is burning.
"否定"是会让人上瘾的
Denial is a powerful thing.
很好 继续装
Well, keep talking.
我才不会上当
I'll have no part of it,
只要会思考的人都不会
nor would any thinking person.
继续思考 律师先生
Keep thinking, Mr. Lawyer.
没人敢反驳上帝的旨意
There's no defense against the will of God.
地狱里更不会有上诉庭
There's no court of appeals in hell.
这里也没什么好辩驳的
There's no defense here, either.
有世界上最多的肥料也不行
Not even with all the fertilizer in the world,
把他们堆的再高也不行
not even if you stack it as high as you can.
最终还不过是几袋臭屎 不是吗?
It's still just bags of shit, isn't it?
有谁想理性地讨论这件事
Those of you who want to discuss this thing...
找出自救的方法的
rationally to find a means of rescue...
欢迎到我这里来
are welcome to join me.
那些想堆狗食的人
Those who want to stack dog food,
请便吧
knock yourselves out.
最好把那些窗户粘起来 越牢越好
We got those windows taped up as best we could.
这应该有用的
It should help.
是啊 你这么想?
Yeah, think so?
管道胶布加狗食袋子
Duct tape and dog food bags.
很糟吗?
That bad?
不怎么好
It's not good.
最瞎的不是盲人 是那些不愿意去看的人
There's none so blind as those who will not see.
睁开你们双眼吧
Open your eyes.
抛开一切条规
Let the scales fall away.
这些都已写进了书中
This has all been written.
《启示录》 第15章
Revelations, chapter 15:
"殿中充满了浓烟"
"And the temple was filled with smoke
"全因神的荣耀"
"from the glory of God
"以及他的神力"
"and from his power,
"于是没人能进殿"
"and no one could enter the temple
"直等到那七位天使
until the seven plagues of...
所降的七灾完毕了"
the seven angels were completed."
你到底说些什么?
Well, what are you saying?
你有什么建议?
What are you proposing?
我们都准备...
That we all prepare...
去见我们的上帝
to meet our Maker.
噢 准备去见狗屎吧!
Oh, prepare to meet shit!
夫人 你的舌头一定是吊在中间了
Lady, your tongue must be hung in the middle
那样它就可以两头摆了
so that it can waggle at both ends.
末日已经到了
The end time has come,
不是在烈火中 而是迷雾中
not in flames, but in mist.
给我过来
Come here!
别激动 后退
Easy! Back off!
不如这样 让你的屁股
How about if your ass prepares...
来见见我的10号工作靴
to meet my size-10 work boot.
怎么样?
How about that?
嘿 没必要说到那份上吧
Hey, there's no call for that.
麦伦 让你的朋友冷静一下
Mellon, please, calm your friend down.
我是想挽救你的灵魂 你个蠢货
I'm trying to save your soul, you stupid man.
- 怀疑者死不改悔 - 没事的
- Doubters will doubt till the end. - It's okay.
不 不好意思 不好意思
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
怪物确实把那个可怜的男孩拖走了
A monstrosity did pull that poor boy away.
雾里的怪物...你怀疑吗?
Things in the mist...do you doubt?
你呢?
Do you?
那就走出去
Then go out.
走出去然后说 "你们好啊"
Go out and say, "How do you do."
闭嘴吧 八婆
Shut up, lady.
看在上帝份上
For God's sakes.
好了 别再说了
Look, you'll have to stop now.
你真的吓着孩子们了
You're scaring the children.
他们就应该被吓吓
They should be scared.
噢 是的 他们应该被吓吓
Oh, yes, they should.
他们美好的 纯洁的童心
Their beautiful, pure little minds
已经被谎言吞噬了
have been corrupted with lies.
谎言
Lies.
全都信奉现代神了
All this talk of a modern God,
甚至无神
or no God.
世上有一位神
There is one God.
犹太人的神
The God of the Israelites.
他是个苛刻的爱报复的神
And he is a stern and vengeful God,
而我们已经亵渎他太长时间了
and we have been mocking him far too long,
今天 他要让我们以血偿还
and now he demands retribution in blood.
是时候表明你们自己了
It is time to declare yourselves.
选择立场
Take sides...
受宽恕的和被诅咒的
the saved and the damned.
读读圣书 它宣扬的是救赎
Read the Good Book. It calls for expiation.
- 血祭! - 什么?
- Blood! - What?
血祭
Blood.
小诺米就是第一个
Little Normie was first,
而现在上帝在召唤剩下的人了
and now God calls the rest of us.
债已经注定
The bill is due.
一定要偿还
It must be paid.
正如亚拍拉罕准备牺牲他的独生子
As Abraham prepared to sacrifice his only son
以证明他对神的忠诚 所以...
to prove his love for God, so...
够了
Enough.
另一个血祭有了
Another down payment.
还债的筹码又多了几分
A few more pennies in the jar.
打得好 我不能扇她嘴巴
Now, that's nice, see. I can't smack her,
你就可以
but it's okay for you.
我 很抱歉
I...I'm sorry everybody,
只是这个女人的《旧约》观点
but this lady's perspective is a little...
让我受不了
too Old Testament for my taste.
他们会来找你的
They'll come for you.
也许就在今夜 黑暗降临的时候
Maybe tonight, when darkness comes.
他们今晚会来
They'll come tonight,
而且会带走某个人
and they'll take someone else.
看看到底会不会
See if they don't.
而一旦他们来了
And when they do,
你们就等着对上帝哭吧
you will cry to God,
那时你们会来求卡莫迪圣母来给你指路的
and you will beg Mother Carmody to show you the way.
那很好
That's fine.
不过在那之前 如果你不闭嘴的话
But until then, if you don't shut up,
我会用这个胶布封住你的嘴
I'll wrap this tape around your mouth.
尽管来试试 奥利·威克斯
You just try it, Ollie Weeks.
还有你 臭婊子...
And you, bitch...
你再打我看看...
you hit me again...
如果你敢的话
if you dare.
在这结束之前 你一定会跪在我面前求我的
You'll be on your knees to me before this is through.
外地来的请注意了
Those of you who aren't local should know
卡莫迪夫人是出了名的...
that Mrs. Carmody is known in town for being...
情绪不稳定
unstable.
不是吧 你到底想要说什么?
No shit. What was your first clue?
嗨
Hi.
什么事 小伙子?
What's up, little dude?
怎么不见你朋友们过来救我们?
How come your friends don't come get us?
他们有坦克什么的 对吧?
They got tanks and stuff, right?
为什么不干脆打个电话给他们?
Why can't you just call 'em?
电话不管用了
Phones don't work.
可是你们没有无线电之类的吗?
But don't you got, like, a radio?
嘿 小冠军 怎么了?
Hey, champ, what's going on?
我想让他们的朋友来救我们
I want their friends to come rescue us.
他们也无能为力 孩子
They would if they could, pal.
他们也是一样被困在这了
They're stuck here just like us.
可是...
But...
啊 伙计们 我们那边需要人手
Shh. Now, guys, we could use a hand over there.
是啊 当然了
Yeah, sure thing.
你 该抬抬屁股了
Troop, off your asses.
- 你还好吧? - 我不喜欢那个疯婆子
- You all right? - I don't like that scary lady.
噢 孩子 我也不喜欢
Oh, man, I don't either.
不过 你知道吗?
But you know what?
也许她也吓坏了
Maybe she's scared too.
你说呢?
You think?
你说妈妈没事吗?
You think Mommy's okay?
比利...
Billy...
真抱歉我总是不听她的话
I'm sorry about the times I was bad to her.
妈妈是非常爱你的
Mommy loves you very much.
我敢打赌她没事
And I'll bet she's fine.
我答应你
And I promise you,
我愿意做任何事 让我们重新回到妈妈那
I'm gonna do everything I can to get us back to her.
- 好吗? - 好吧
- Okay? - 'Kay.
- 真的? - 嗯
- Yeah? - 'Kay.
那么 我们可以用煤油加拖把
So, we can use the charcoal fluid and the mops
做成火把
to make torches.
还有我们这里有刀什么的
And we've got knives and stuff, God knows.
这可能是个比较蠢的问题 伯德 不过...
This may be a silly question, Bud, but...
你们有备支枪放在店里吗?
do you happen to have a gun in the store?
这里? 没有 拜托
Here? No. Please.
这...这可不是洛杉机
This...this isn't Los Angeles.
我有支猎枪 可是在车里
I've got a shotgun in my truck.
我可以试着取来 如果你想的话
I could try for it if you want.
噢 天 我可不认为那是个好主意
Oh, God, I don't think that'd be a good idea,
科内尔先生
Mr. Cornell.
等一下
Hold on.
这支枪 嗯...
This gun, um...
是我老公给我防身的
my husband's idea.
他经常出差在外
He's away on business a lot.
它甚至还没上膛
It's not even loaded.
不上膛可没什么用 夫人
Ain't much use unloaded, ma'am.
你懂得怎么用?
You know how to use that?
啊 我在射击场试过一次
Well, I shot it once on a pistol range.
打中过几下靶子
Hit the target a few times.
那么 我们有把枪了
So, we got a gun.
有谁懂得如何开枪吗?
Anybody know how to shoot it?
我是说 打得很好
Well, I mean?
我懂
I do.
你?
You?
奥利 这可不是玩
Ollie. Please.
定点射击
Some target shooting.
94年州冠军
State champion in '94.
- 这是发疯 如果出去的话 - 让我们过去
- You're crazy if you go out there! - Let us pass!
让我们过去 让开!
Let us pass, please!
让咱们先好好聊聊再说
Let's just talk this thing through.
已经谈过了 而且也做了决定 我们要离开
We have, and we've made our decision. We're leaving.
嘿 麦基先生急着走
Hey, Mr. Mackey's gonna...
因为有烧鸡在烤架上等着他
barbecue some chicken on the gas grill.
为什么我们不坐下来再...
Why don't we just sit down and just...
什么 让你继续在那讲演?
What, and let you keep on talking?
不 我已在法庭上
No, I've been in far too many...
听得太多了
courtrooms to fall for that.
你已经抢走了
You've already psyched out...
半打我的人了
half a dozen of my people already.
你的人?
Your people?
你这算什么话?
What kind of talk is that?
他们就是他们 仅此而已
They're people, that's all.
现在...现在 听着 大家
Now...now listen, everyone.
我们正经历一场大灾难
We are experiencing some kind of disaster.
我不确定到底是人为的抑或自然性的
I don't know whether it's man-made or natural,
但是我敢确定 那绝不是什么超自然的
but I do know that it's definitely not supernatural
或救赎之类 无意冒犯 卡莫迪夫人
or biblical, and, no offense, Mrs. Carmody,
但是我们唯一自救的方法
but the only way we're gonna help ourselves
就是寻找求援
is to seek rescue.
我们要出去
We're going out.
布伦特 听着
Brent, look.
我不打算再讨论这事了
I'm not discussing this any further.
我知道 我只想请你帮个忙
I know. I just want to ask a favor.
把这个绑到你的腰上
Tie this around your waist.
为什么?
What for?
它会告诉我们 你们至少走了300英尺
It'll let us know you got at least 300 feet.
我来做
I'll do it.
你想加入他们?
Are you throwing in with them?
我? 才不是呢
Me? No thanks.
我想你那个老兄有点太紧张了
I think your man there is a little too tightly wound.
这样会死人的
Gonna get somebody killed.
不过我想 我们会用得着你的猎枪
But I'm thinkin' we could use that shotgun of yours.
我进来的时候刚好看到你泊车
I saw where you parked when I pulled in.
红色小卡车 对吧? 远端入口?
Red pickup, right? Far entrance?
孩子 你可真是个豹子胆
Son, you got brass balls.
子弹在表盘旁的储物柜里
The shells are in the glove compartment.
开回来
Drive it back.
好的
All right.
只要保证他们缓放绳子就行
Just see they're paying out this line.
绳子放完 我就会割断它
Line's up, I'll cut her loose,
这样你们就明白了
just so you understand.
好的
Yeah.
真的没办法劝你放弃吗?
You sure there's no way I can talk you out of this?
戴维...
David...
外面没什么东西 雾里没东西
there's nothing out there. Nothing in the mist.
万一你错了怎么办?
What if you're wrong?
那么 我想...
Then, I guess...
玩笑终于开到我头上了
the joke would be on me after all.
我们会叫救援回来的
We're gonna send back help.
你们会死在外面 全部
You'll die out there. All of you.
嘿 疯婆子 我也信仰上帝
Hey, crazy lady, I believe in God too.
只是我不认为 他是那种嗜血成性的混蛋
I just don't think he's the bloodthirsty asshole
是你把他说成这样的
you make him out to be.
好吧 带着你的观点
Well, you take that up with the devil...
去跟魔鬼说吧
when you run into him.
没事的时候跟他好好讨论讨论
You just chat it over at your leisure.
好了 咱们出发吧 直奔镇中心
Well, let's strike out toward the center of town.
保持宽松
Keep it loose.
很好 放松
Nice and easy.
继续放
Keep going.
快看
Look.
还在走
It's going.
他们做的不赖
They're doing good.
放它下来
Put it down!
快拉
Ohh! Pull!
噢 我的天! 我被拽滑动了!
Oh, my God! I'm slippin'!
拉啊! 向后拉! 向后拉! 向后拉!
Pull! Back up! Back up! Back up!
放开
Get it off!
噢 我的天
Oh, my God.
- 噢 妈的 - 血!
- Aw, sh...- Blood!
噢 天哪!
Oh, my God!
噢 我的天啊!
割断绳子
Cut the rope!
关上门
Shut the door!
这下 看到了吧?
Now do you see?
这下 相信了吧?
Now do you believe?
大概还有半个小时天就黑了
About a half-hour of daylight left.
这些工作灯怎么样?
Guys, how's it going with these work lights?
我们在把它们装好
We're gettin' 'em rigged up all right.
好的 来检查一下
Yeah, check it out.
好了 好了 省着点 省着点
All right, all right. Save it, save it.
这些电池都是没有充满的
These batteries ain't topped up.
开着灯会让电耗得更快
You turn the lights on, it's gonna drain 'em quick.
有多快?
How quick?
- 五分钟 十分钟的样子 - 是啊 如果能用的话
- Five minutes, maybe ten. - Yeah, if that.
嗯 那就紧急状态再启用
Okay, emergencies only.
等到有东西闯进来的时候
If something gets in the store.
噢 你吓死我了
Holy Jesus, you scared the shit outta me.
啊 萨利 对不起 真的
Oh, Sally, I'm sorry, really.
我想我进来应该打声招呼
I thought I'd come in and say hi...
看看你过得怎么样
and see how you were holding up.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
勉勉强强 你呢?
Barely. How about you?
我在担心我的家人
I'm worried about my folks, I guess.
你知道 他们住在索姆路
You know, they live up on Shorm Road.
离这里不到5英里
That's less than five miles from here.
你家里人呢?
How 'bout yours?
他们现在不在镇上
Well, they're out of town right now.
他们在我波士顿的阿姨那里 所以...
They're at my aunt's in Boston, so...
很幸运啊 那就是说他们都很好
That's lucky. That means they're okay.
但愿吧
I hope so.
那...
So...
你什么时候出发?
how soon you shipping out?
几个星期之后吧
Uh, couple weeks.
害怕到那儿吗?
Scared about going over there?
嗯
Yeah.
嘿 韦恩
Hey, Wayne?
为什么你从来不约我出去?
How come you never asked me out?
中学的时候我们一直都在调情
We flirted all through high school.
我知道你是喜欢我的
I know you like me.
为什么不跟我说呢?
So how come?
我想 是我笨吧
I'm stupid, I guess.
啊 真是的 对不起
Oh, shit! I'm sorry.
别说对不起 我只是...
Don't be. I just...
我只是不想这样
I just didn't really want it to happen like this,
你明白吗?
you know?
工作的时候 糟糕的更衣室里
Some shitty locker room at work.
那我们能不能在这里待一会儿?
Can we just stay in here a while, then?
我的意思是 就...就你和我
I mean, just...just you and me.
停车场的灯亮了
The parking lot lamps turned on.
那是定时的
They're on a timer.
那应该是另外一根有电的线吧
Must be a different one that's live.
也许我们能牵根线过去
Maybe we could tie into them somehow,
弄些电过来
get some electricity in here.
那意味着要出去
That'd mean walking out the door.
嘎!天啊!
Gaaaahhhh! God!
啊 天啊! 啊 天啊!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
戴维! 戴维!
David! David!
看!
Look!
天哪
My God.
那些东西是虫子吗?
Are those bugs?
从没见过这样的
Not like any I've ever seen.
"有蝗虫从烟中出来
"They came out of the smoke,
"飞落到大地上
"locusts upon the earth,
"有能力赐给它们
"and unto them was given power
"好像地上的蝎子的能力一样
even as the scorpions of the earth have power."
看这些长刺的怪物
Look at those stingers.
老天爷
Dear God.
我靠!
Holy shit!
麦伦 把后面的灯也打开
Mellon, get the ones in the back!
天哪 我觉得它们被灯光吸引过来了
God, I think they're attracted to the light.
小心 小心 小心!
Look out, look out, look out!
灯! 把灯关掉!
The light! Douse the light!
小心! 小心!
Look out! Look out!
走! 快走!
Move! Move!
灯 灯 灯 灯 灯!
Light, light, light, light, light!
"有大声音从殿中出来
"And there came a voice from the temple
"向那七位天使说
"saying to the seven angels,
"你们去
"'Go your ways
"把盛神大怒的七碗
and pour out the vials of the...
倒在地上"
wrath of God upon the earth.'"
奥利 这块玻璃撑不住了!
Ollie, the glass is gonna give!
妈的!
Shit!
我的妈呀 他们把所有灯都开了!
Oh, my God, they turned on all the lights!
- 吉姆! 麦伦! - 火!
- Jim! Mellon! - Fire!
- 火! 打火机! - 把灯关了!
- Fire! Lighter! - Douse the lights!
快点 快点!
Come on, come on!
萨利 小心!
Sally, look out!
不!
No!
让我看看 让我看看 亲爱的 让我看看
Let me see. Let me see, sweetheart, let me see.
没事的 你会没事的 你会好的
No, you're gonna be okay. You're gonna be okay.
让我看看 让我看看
Let me see. Let me see.
你很好 你会没事的
You're fine. You're gonna be okay.
把打火机给我! 点火!
Give me the lighter! Put it on fire!
快!
Come on!
该死的这是儿童安全型的!
Goddamn childproofing sons of bitches!
开枪! 开枪啊!
Oh, shoot it! Shoot it!
打死它! 打死它!
Shoot it! Shoot it!
不行! 我会连窗子一起打破的!
I can't! I'll smash the window!
天啊!
God!
噢 我的天哪!
Oh, God! Ohh!
快! 快!
Go! Go!
趴下!
Get down!
妈的!
Shit!
奥利 你想让灯开着还是关着?
Ollie, you want these lights on or off?
就开着吧
Leave 'em on.
噢 天啊!
Oh, God!
啊! 啊! 杀了它!
Ohh! Ohhh! Kill it!
拿火把来! 把它们赶出去!
Bring torches! Bring something to keep 'em out!
快!
Come on.
萨利!
Sally!
该死的 灭火器在哪?
Where are the goddamn extinguishers?
烧到了! 烧到了! 烧到了!
Get it! Get it! Get it!
拿火把来 窗口这边需要火把!
Bring torches. We need torches at the window!
堵住那个口子!
Plug that hole!
爸爸!
Dad!
趴下! 趴下! 趴下来!
Down! Down! Lay down!
我的生命...
My life...
我的命给你 你的愿望就达成了
my life for you, your will be done.
爸爸!
Daddy!
虫子! 爸爸!
Bugs! Daddy!
- 别过去! 比利! - 爸爸!
- Nooooo! Billy! - Daddy!
- 比利! - 爸爸!
- Billy! - Daddy!
比利!
Billy!
爸爸!
Dad!
比利 回来
Billy, come back here.
- 爸爸! - 比利 回来!
- Dad! - Billy, please!
比利!
Billy!
快 搬过来!
Come on, let's move it!
再过来几个人帮忙
Somebody please come over here and help.
这里有些胶带!
Here's some tape!
我在这儿 我在这儿 别担心
I'm right here. I'm right here. Don't worry.
快把拿毯子过来!
Hurry up with the blankets!
好痛啊! 帮帮我 求你了!
It hurts so bad! Please!
真的很痛!
It hurts so bad!
堵住这里
Block it up here.
再弄几袋过来!
Get me some more bags!
赶走了吗? 我们把它们都赶走了吗?
Did we get 'em? Did we get 'em all?
她说对了
She was right.
她说过会发生这种事的
She said that it would happen like this.
她说过它们会在晚上来袭击我们的
She said that they would come at night.
她说过有人会死的
She told us someone would die.
妈妈
Mommy.
嘘 嘘 嘘 没事了
Ohh, shh, shh, shh. It's okay.
没事了 只是一个梦
It's okay, it was just a dream.
只是一个恶梦
It's just a bad dream.
我要妈妈
I want my mommy.
我知道
I know.
我知道 你肯定很想你妈妈
I know. Of course you do.
我想回家
I wanna go home.
睡吧
Just sleep.
到明天一切都会好的
Everything'll be better in the morning.
他挺喜欢你的
Think he likes you.
唉 我真的不想骗他
Well, I hate that I had to lie to him.
你有孩子吗?
You have kids?
没有
No.
我一直想要一个 可是...
I always wanted to, but...
事情并不是那么顺利
things haven't been working out.
现在我想也许没生孩子是对的
Right now I'm thinking maybe that's for the best.
今天晚上我看到一些东西飞到店里来
I saw creatures fly into the store tonight that...
它们本不该存在于这个世界上的
they shouldn't exist.
我还以为我是在橡胶房里呢
I keep thinking I'm gonna wake up in a rubber room.
你不是一个人在那儿
You're not alone in that.
我们都跟你在一起
We're all right there with you.
这还没有完 不是吗?
This isn't gonna end, is it?
戴维
David.
乔的情况恶化了
It's Joe. He's getting worse.
乔
Joe.
你觉得怎么样 伙计?
How you holdin' up, partner?
戴维...是你吗?
David...is that you?
嗯 伙计 觉得怎么?
Yeah, pal, how you doin'?
不好 他的情况不好
It's bad. He's bad.
我从来都不知道有什么能让我疼成这样的
Didn't know anything could hurt like this.
如果你们帮不了我...
If you guys can't help me...
你...你们就帮我结束它 好吗?
you...you gotta end it, okay?
奥利不是有把枪吗?
Ollie's got that gun, right?
- 啊? - 不 不行
- Right? - No. No way.
你不能让我受这种罪 兄弟
You can't fuck with me on this, bro.
我受不了了
Not with me like this.
我自己来
I'll do it.
把枪给我就行了
Just give me the gun.
- 我们还没到那地步 好不? - 求求你们了!
- We're not there yet, okay? - Oh, please!
乔 你听我说
Joe, now, listen.
伙计...
Pal...
我们去弄点药回来
we're gonna work something out.
你再坚持一会儿 好吗?
I just need you to hang in a little longer, okay?
做得到吗?
Can we do that?
陪着他 我很快回来
Stay with him. I'll be back.
哈蒂 我要去洗手间
Hattie, I need to go to the bathroom.
你看着比利好吗?
Will you watch Billy?
哈蒂
Hattie.
有没有看见什么东西?
See anything?
大概四点的时候最后一只虫子也飞走了
The last of those bugs went away about four.
快要天亮了
Dawn's coming.
有什么想法?
What's on your mind?
关于乔
It's Joe.
要是我们不给他弄点抗生素的话
We don't get him on some serious antibiotics,
他肯定会因为感染死掉的
he's gonna die of infection.
而且他的情况太糟糕了 他需要止痛药
Plus he needs painkillers in the worst way.
我...我们这里只有乙醇和阿司匹林
All...all we got here is liquor and aspirin.
你...你们想到隔壁的药房去?
You thinkin'about goin'to that pharmacy next door?
爱琳·瑞普说那里有磺胺嘧啶银
Irene Reppler says they've got Silvadene...
你知道 那是治烧伤的
you know, the stuff they use in burn wards.
她知道那药放在哪里
She knows where they keep it.
等等
Slow down.
你们不会真的想这么做吧?
You can't actually be thinkin' of doin' this.
我想得更远
I'm also thinkin' beyond that.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
我是说永远离开这儿
I mean permanently.
为什么? 这里有足够的食物!
Why? We got plenty to eat!
要是那些怪物
What happens when one of those things...
冲破窗户怎么办?
decides to break through this window?
我说的是那种大个的
I'm talkin' one of the big ones,
就像杀了诺姆的那种
like the one that killed Norm.
对 火把也不是
Yeah, and that flaming torch idea...
那么好使 是吗?
didn't work so well, did it?
我们差不多快把这家店都给烧了
We almost burned the goddamn store down.
哈蒂死了
It's Hattie.
这里?
Here?
好 轻点 现在 轻点
All right, gently, now. Gently.
一...二...三
One...two...three.
我不知道她躺在那里多久了
I don't know how long she was there like that,
就躺在我们身边
lying there next to us.
我以为她在睡觉
I thought she was sleeping.
我有辆车
I got my 4-wheel drive.
就在外面
It's out there.
你...你们要走?
Y...you're talking about leaving?
嗯 我们...
Well, we...
要先去一趟药房
should hit the pharmacy first.
得给伤员弄点药回来
We gotta bring back supplies for the injured.
我是说 如果不这样
I mean, if we don't,
乔·伊格尔就要死了
Joe Eagleton's gonna die,
我们不能让这种情况发生
and we can't let that happen.
但在那之后...
But after that...
看 我的车可以坐8个人
look, my Land Cruiser can hold eight people.
我想一直朝南面开 直到燃料耗尽
I say we drive south as far as the fuel takes us
然后设法摆脱这场雾
and try to get clear of this mist.
就这样?
That's it?
这就是你的计划?
That's the plan?
- 这就是我所想到的 - 不 你不能那样做
- That's what I got. - No, you can't mean it.
不能步诺顿和他的那组人的后尘
Not after what happened to Norton and his group.
不 不 不 阿曼达 你想想
No, no, no. Amanda, think.
诺顿从这里大概走出了200英尺
Norton got over 200 feet from this store.
那是放出的绳子的长度
That's how much rope played out.
我的车停在只有这个距离一半远的地方
I'm parked half that distance from here.
可是谁知道这雾扩散得有多快呢?
But who knows how far this mist has spread?
可能已经遍布整个东海岸了
It could be the entire eastern seaboard.
是呀 也许都已经遍布整个世界了
Yeah, it could be the whole world, for all we know.
横竖都是一死 不是吗?
Wouldn't make us any less dead, now, would it?
我们只有一把枪
We have one gun.
- 还有多少? - 十发
- How many rounds? - We got ten left.
十发
Ten rounds. Jesus.
行 就十发
Okay, so ten.
想再听一个离开这的理由吗?
Want another reason to get the hell out of here?
我给你们最好的吧
I'll give you the best one.
她
Her.
卡莫迪夫人
Mrs. Carmody.
她就是我们这儿的吉姆·琼斯 (美国邪教人民圣殿教的创办人)
She's our very own Jim Jones.
我想在人们受她蛊惑之前
I'd like to leave before people...
离开这里
start drinking the Kool-Aid.
他是对的
He's right.
人们越是恐惧不安 她的话就越是有理
Flakier people get, the better she's gonna look.
我可不吃她那一套 这明显只是她自己胡说八道
No, I don't buy that. It's obvious she's nuts.
也许有小部分人很信服她所说的 但是...
Look, a few people maybe, but...
不 有四个 她现在正在训诫他们
No, I count four. She's preachin'to 'em right now.
到明天中午 她会再有四个跟随者
By noon, she'll have four more.
到明天晚上 当那些怪物再来
By tomorrow night, when those things come back,
她就可以举行集会了
she'll have a congregation,
到那时我们就会开始担心
and then we can start worryin' about...
她准备把谁当祭品...
who she's gonna sacrifice
好让她们好过一点
to make it all better.
你吗 阿曼达?
You, Amanda?
还是我的儿子?
My little boy?
他是对的
He's right.
你本来就不相信人性本善 不是吗?
You don't have much faith in humanity, do you?
从来不信
None whatsoever.
我无法接受
I can't accept that.
人本质上是善良的 是正派的
People are basically good, decent.
我的天啊 戴维 我们是一个文明社会
My God, David, we're a civilized society.
当然了 只要这机器还在正常运转
Sure, as long as the machines are workin'
只要你还能拔9-1-1
and you can dial 9-1-1,
但是现在你把这些都拿走
but you take those things away,
把他们扔进黑暗里
you throw people in the dark,
然后把他们吓得尿裤子了
you scare the shit out of them,
就不再有所谓的准则了
no more rules,
你会看到他们会变得有多么不开化
you'll see how primitive they get.
当你把他们吓怕了的时候
You scare people badly enough,
你让他们做什么都可以
you can get 'em to do anything.
只要谁承诺有出路 或别的什么方法
They'll turn to whoever promises a solution,
他们就会跟着他
or whatever.
奥利 帮我说说话
Ollie, please, back me up here.
我也想
I wish I could.
作为一个物种 我们从根本上是愚蠢的
As a species, we're fundamentally insane.
如果房间里多于两个人 我们就会选择立场
Put more than two of us in a room, we pick sides
然后开始想方设法置对方于死地
and start dreaming up reasons to kill one another.
你觉得我们为什么要发明政治和宗教?
Why do you think we invented politics and religion?
啊 老天 那是...
Oh, Jesus, that's just...
错的
wrong.
瞧 我们并不是要现在就决定所有的事情
Look, nobody has to decide anything now, okay?
当务之急是...
First things first...
去药房
the pharmacy.
那会是我们的试验
That'll be our test run.
行吗?
Okay?
不会有事的 你是个男子汉 比利
It's all right, Big Bill.
我会给你带一些漫画回来的
I'm gonna bring you back some comic books.
我不要漫画
I don't want them.
我要你留在这里
I want you to stay here.
我不会去很久的
I won't be gone long.
就...就在隔壁
Just...just next door.
嘿 你会很安全的
Hey, you'll be safe.
爸爸...
Daddy...
爸爸 外面有怪物
Daddy, there are things out there.
怪物...
Things...
我知道 但是白天的时候不会有很多的
Yeah. There's a lot less of 'em in the daytime.
它们会等着
They'll wait.
它们会在雾里你看不到的地方等着
They'll wait in the mist where you can't see 'em,
然后等你出去还没回来的时候...
and then when you go and can't get back in...
它们就会把你吃掉的!
they'll come and eat you up!
爸爸 别去!
Daddy, don't go!
我会回来的
I'll be back.
小男子汉...
Big Bill...
我保证
I promise.
我会回来的 然后带你回家
I'll be back, and then I'm gonna take you home.
好吗?
All right?
我们一起回家
Together, we're going home.
如果发生了什么事 不管是什么
If something happens, anything at all,
你就赶快逃走
you cut and run.
为了你的孩子你爬也要爬回来
You get your ass back in here, for your boy's sake.
如果我有什么不测
If something happens to me,
我想让你来照顾比利...
I want you to take care of Billy...
尽你所能 多一分钟是一分钟
best as you can, and long as you can.
车是你的了
Land Cruiser's yours now.
你...你带他离开这里
You...you get him out of here.
一直往前开
You just keep drivin'.
你们要去哪呀 戴维·德雷顿先生?
Where do you think you're going,Mr.David Drayton?
你就这么急着想让你的儿子变成孤儿?
Are you so anxious to make your boy an orphan?
我的儿子不用你来操心
My boy is no concern of yours.
听着
Listen up.
我们要去药房
We're going to the pharmacy.
我们要弄一些药品回来
We're gonna bring back some supplies.
当然 还有可能 有人被困在那里
Also, there may be people trapped...
需要救助
over there who need help.
听着 各位 听好!
Listen, folks, listen!
我们不是要拼命
We're not gonna take any chances.
如果有什么麻烦
If there's any trouble,
我们会马上返回超市
we'll come straight back here to the supermarket.
然后把地狱来的魔鬼引到我们头上
And bring the fiends of hell...
那时可真得谢谢你们啊
down on our heads, thank you.
她是对的
She's right.
你们会让它们注意到我们的
You'll make 'em notice us.
你们会把它们引来的
You'll make 'em come.
为什么你们就不能让这儿继续好好的呢?
Why can't you just leave well enough alone?
小姐 这就叫"好好的"?
Lady, this what you call 'well enough"?
你要阻止我们?
You wanna stop us?
那你最好给博比解释一下
You better explain to Bobby here
为什么我们
why we're not bringin' painkillers...
不给他哥哥拿止痛药
and medicine back for his brother.
我去 就算只有我一个
I'm goin', even if I have to go alone.
年轻人 你会死在那里的
You'll die out there, young man.
你走出这扇门 然后就会被撕成碎片的
You'll walk out that door and be torn to shreds,
然后你那见鬼的傲慢
and then your hell-bound pride...
会把它们引向我们剩下的人
will have them come get the rest of us.
没错 它们会回来找我们所有人
Yes, they'll come back for all of us,
就像这位女士说的那样
just like this good lady said.
你们想让这一切发生吗?
Do you want that to happen, people?
- 不想! - 不! 不想! 不想!
- No! - No! No! No!
好 就是这种狂妄自大
Well, it is this kind of hubris
引来了主的愤怒
that brought the wrath of God in the first place.
这种傲慢和挑衅...
This kind of pride and defiance of...
闭嘴 你这个可怜虫!
Shut up, you miserable buzzard!
你这个老婊子!
You old bitch!
用石头去打不跟你站一边的人 你最在行了
Stoning people who piss you off is perfectly okay.
他们在圣经里也是这样做的 不是吗?
They do it in the Bible, don't they?
我还有很多豆罐呢
And I got lots of peas.
戴维 快 如果你要去 现在就是时候
David, please, if you want to go, now's the time.
你们几个军人 去不去?
How 'bout it, Army?
军人会出力吗?
Any help from the armed forces?
我去
I'll go.
吉姆·格朗丹
Jim Grondin.
我教过你的 不是吗?
I had you in school, didn't I?
是的 夫人 我和我姐姐波林
Yes'm, me and my sister Pauline.
真是一对后进生啊
Pair of underachievers.
我跟你后面 吉姆
After you, Jim.
好吧 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
妈的
Oh, shit.
就这些人吗? 人都齐了吗?
That it? That's everybody?
去的人都准备好了 我们走了
Everybody that's goin'.
- 嗯 - 好
- Yep. - Okay.
一个跟一个走 听清楚了吗?
Single file, one by one, all right?
我们把这事解决了
Let's get this thing over with.
走
Let's go.
- 我跟着你 - 好
- After you. - Yes.
走在一起
Stay together.
你知道什么?
You know what?
卡莫迪夫人 你帮不上忙
Mrs. Carmody, you're not helping.
- 闭他妈嘴! - 你闭嘴!
- Shut the hell up! - You shut up!
电池省着用
Save the batteries.
该死
Shit.
他们就这样让门开着
They left the doors propped open.
也许有怪物来过吧?
Think something got in?
我们只拿我们需要的
Let's just...get what we need,
别管那么多
get the hell outta here.
好 就这样
Yeah. Let's do that.
药在那边尽头的小隔间里
The meds are over at the end there, in the cubicle.
你能不能别搞出这种事?
Will you not do that?
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
磺胺嘧啶银在哪?
Where's that Silvadene?
在戴维后面
It's over behind David.
在冰箱里 过去看看
In the fridge. Check there.
磺胺嘧啶银 拿到了
Silvadene. Got it.
- 好 - 奥利 我们要找什么?
- Good. - Ollie, what are we lookin' for?
- 青霉素 - 好的
- Penicillin. - Yeah.
强力的抗生素都行
Any strong antibiotics.
嗯
Yeah.
像维柯丁和复方羟氢可待因之类的止痛药
Pain meds like Vicodin or OxyContin.
复方羟氢可待因!
OxyContin!
盐酸?
Hydrochloride?
青霉素
Penicillin.
伙计们
Guys.
快点 我听到一些声音
Hurry it up. I hear something.
什么?
What?
一些他妈的很怪的声音
Somethin' fuckin' weird.
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
噢 天啊!
Oh, God!
不 不要
No. Oh, no.
啊 不
Oh, nooooo.
妈的
Oh, fuck.
看 那儿还有一个
Look. There's another one.
- 噢 天啊 - 不
- Oh, my God. - No, no, no.
啊 不要 不要啊
Oh, no, no.
大家 我们现在就走吧
Guys, let's get out of here now.
真他妈该死!
Holy shit!
妈的! 妈的! 他妈的!
Shit! Shit! Oh, shit!
对不起! 对不起啊! 救救我!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! Help me!
主啊! 救救他吧!
Good Lord! Help him!
狗娘养的!
Son of a bitch!
这些东西扯不下来!
This stuff ain't comin' off!
他被粘到这该死的柱子上了!
Oh, man! He's glued to this fuckin' post!
是我们的错
It's our fault.
都是我们的错
It's all our fault.
真的粘得很牢
It's really stuck.
主啊 我能感觉到它们!
God, I can feel 'em!
我能感觉到它们!
I can feel 'em!
噢 天呀!
Oh, my God! Jesus!
噢 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
啊 我...
Ohh! I...
还有更多呀!
There's more!
那儿还有一只! 打它!
There's another one! Hit it!
这到底是什么鬼东西啊?
What the hell is that stuff?
奥利! 那边有一只!
Ollie! One over there!
奥利 那边!
Ollie, there!
知道了!
Got it!
那儿 瞧 那儿! 开枪! 开枪!
There, there, there! Shoot! Shoot!
妈的!
Shit!
看到了吗?
See 'em?
博比!
Bobby!
坚持住 伙计! 坚持住!
Hold on, man! Hold on!
- 坚持住 伙记! - 把线砍断!
- Hold on, man! - Cut the strand!
救我!
Help me!
我们快走!
Let's get out of here!
- 皮带! 谁有皮带? - 我有皮带!
- A belt! Who's got a belt? - I got a belt!
我抓住他了 我抓住他了 抓好
I got him, I got him. Hold on.
拉紧!
Pull it tight!
看! 看!
Look! Look!
灯!
Light!
啊!
God!
我们得离开这里! 快!
We gotta get outta here! Come on!
走 走 走 走!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
小心 小心 小心!
Watch it, watch it, watch it!
我们走吧!
Let's get out of here!
好了 走 走 走 走! 快!
All right, go, go, go, go, go, go! Come on!
快!
Come on!
噢 天哪!
Oh, my God!
奥利! 奥利!
Ollie! Ollie!
杀了它! 杀了它!
Kill it! Kill it!
混蛋!
Fuckers!
啊 不要! 天哪 他死了!
Oh, no! Oh, God, he's dead!
他已经死了! 快离开这里! 走 快走!
He's dead! Get out of here! Let's go, let's go!
德雷顿 来 来呀 快走!
Drayton, come on, come on, come on!
走吧 德雷顿 他已经死了!
Come on, Drayton, he's dead!
快!
Come on!
开门!
Open the door!
博比呢?
Where's Bobby?
爸爸!
Daddy!
把门锁上!
Close up the doors!
快!
Hurry up!
发生什么了?
What happened?
他们死了! 他们全死了!
They're dead! They're all dead!
...赎罪 因为我们看见
...expiation, because we have seen
大地受虐于鞭子甚至蝎子鞭
the earth scourged with whips and scorpions.
我们看见了大地从她嘴里吐出
We have seen the earth vomit forth from her lips
这些恶梦般的
obscenities and profanities of...
肮脏与亵渎
such nightmare proportions.
全因这些邪恶的 潜伏着的灵魂
And for these evil, lurking spirits,
全因这些邪恶的人们...
and for these evil people...
我睡了多久了?
How long was I out?
大半天了
Most of the day.
你一回到这里
You just came over here to...
倒下就睡着了
lay down and went to sleep.
是昏倒了 好像是这样的
Just passed out, is more like it.
什么能阻止这个大淫妇?
What will stop this Great Whore?
我昏迷了一会儿
Just shut down for a while.
对不起
Sorry.
它将怎样收场?
How will it end?
赎罪!
Expiation!
赎罪! 你们还记得昨天...
Expiation! Do you remember yesterday when...
乔怎么样了?
How's Joe?
死了 在你睡着的时候 乔因为过度烧伤死了
Dead. Joe died of his burns while you were asleep.
我们太晚了
We were just too late.
我告诉过你们结果会是这样的!
I told you this would come!
天哪 我还以为是我在梦到她的声音呢
Oh, God, I thought I was dreaming her voice.
这可不是梦
No dream.
她正煽动人们的情绪
She's getting people whipped up.
那个可怜的女孩死了
That poor girl is dead,
那个男孩也被烧伤了 正躺在里屋里!
and that boy is burnt in the back room!
她在让他们相信她是通灵圣母
She's got 'em believing she's a psychic,
是上帝的信使
she has a direct line with God.
她们怎么就不停一停? 女人总是喋喋不休
Why wouldn't they? Woman never shuts up.
像卡斯特罗发表过的那些演说那样
Like those speeches Castro used to make.
奥利说你在考虑离开
Ollie says you're thinking of leaving.
算我一个
I'm in.
不 很抱歉
No. Sorry.
我是说 你也看到
I mean, come on, you saw...
博比和迈克的结局了
what happened to Bobby...Mike...
我不会...
I won't...
再那样做了 我负不起这个责任
do that again. I won't be responsible.
你要再考虑一下
You might want to reconsider that.
什么...什么会把这些罪恶
What will...what will keep these evil,
这些可憎的东西拒之门外?
these abominations at bay?
什么能让它们滚开?
What will keep them away?
"石头不会藏匿它们
"The rock will not hide them.
枯树也不是它们的藏身之所"
The dead tree gives no shelter."
什么会终结它? 告诉我
What will end it? Let me hear it.
- 赎罪! - 我们在讨论什么?
- Expiation! - What are we talking about?
- 赎罪! - 再说一遍 虔诚地!
- Expiation! - Say it again like you mean it!
赎罪!
Expiation!
欢迎收看《芝麻街》
Welcome to Sesame Street.
今天的话题是"赎罪"
Today's word is "expiation."
哈利路亚! 哈利路亚!
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
那人从在药房起就不大对劲
That boy hasn't been right since the pharmacy.
他的思维一下子终止了 没了
His mind's just snapped. Gone.
这还没到两天呢
Hasn't even been two days.
两天都不到呀
Not even two days.
我可不会让我的余生在这里过
I'm not spendin' the rest of my life here,
我会出去的
I'll tell you what.
我可以悄悄的拿几袋食品
I can quietly gather up some bags of groceries
藏到靠门的
and hide them up at...
一个收银台里
one of the check stands by the door.
这是你的主意 你的车
It was your idea. It's your vehicle.
我们就等你的决定了
It'll be your call.
就算是死我也要出去搏一搏
I'd rather die out there trying...
而不是在这里干等着
than in here waiting.
谁来救它们? 没有人
Who will save them? No one.
石头不会藏匿它们
The rocks will not hide them.
我想知道我们现在要面对是什么
I want some idea of what we're up against.
我想知道这雾是怎么回事
I want to know what this mist is.
我要跟那些士兵谈谈
I want to talk to the soldiers.
士兵? 为什么?
Soldiers? What's that gonna do?
在药房的时候 你也听到那个宪兵说的了
You heard what that M.P. said at the pharmacy.
戴维 我还不确定他那时候到底有没有说话
David, I'm not even sure I knew he was talking.
当时的情况乱哄哄的
The situation was insane.
他说对不起
He said he was sorry.
他用的是"对不起"吧?
Wasn't that the word he used..."sorry"?
没错 他说那是他们的错 不是吗?
That's right. He said it was their fault, right?
他那是什么意思?
What did he mean by that?
那正是我们要弄明白的
That's what we're gonna find out.
爱琳 请你陪着比利
Irene, stay with Billy, please.
第17章!
Verse 17!
"...把碗倒在空中
"...poured out his vial into the air,
"就有大声音
"and there came a great voice
从殿中的宝座上出来 说
"out of the temple of heaven from the throne,saying,
""成了! 成了!"
"'It is done! It is done!'
"又有闪电 又有声音
"And there were voices and lightning,
雷轰 大地震"
and thunders, and a great earthquake."
对! 归投我吧!
Yes! Come to me!
什么事?
What?
- 你的朋友呢? - 我没看到他们
- Where's your friends? - I ain't seen 'em.
这商店不大 弄丢一个人可不是容易的事
Not that big a store. It's kinda hard to lose.
我说过 我没看到他们
I ain't seen 'em, I said.
我又不是他们的监护人
I look like their keeper?
你想从我这里得到什么?
What do you want from me?
你知道这雾是怎么回事吗?
What do you know about this mist?
我什么都不知道 这跟我一点关系都没有
I don't know nothin'.I got nothin' to do with it.
那个宪兵在药房里 被蜘蛛钻出他的皮肤以前
That's not what the M.P. said in the pharmacy
可不是这样说的
before the spiders came out of his skin.
他们不在店里
They're not in the store.
我们没找的地方就只有储物间了
The only place we haven't looked is the loading dock.
...因为你们知道
...because you know.
今晚你看到了主的真容
You saw the good face of God tonight.
是吗? 告诉我们
Yes? Tell us.
这里有个老人目睹了主!
Here is an old man who has seen!
是的 他看见了!
Yes, he has seen!
阿门
Amen.
我还想说 我会跟你们一起
And I want to say, do I want to walk with you
走到我主的跟前吗?
into my Father's hands?
莫拉莱士
Morales.
唐纳德逊
Donaldson.
伙计们...
Guys...
他们只能在这里了
It's the only place they can be.
什么?
What?
他们不可能凭空消失的
Couldn't just disappear.
看 我告诉过你们
Look, I told you, okay,
我不知道他们在哪...
I don't know where they are...
我没想到他们真的自杀了
I didn't think they'd do it.
他们说过会自杀的 而我只是...
They said they would do it, and I just...
我把宪兵在药房里说的话告诉了他们
I told them what the M.P. said at the pharmacy,
然后他们发誓说要自杀
and they swore they'd do it.
我只是...我没想过他们会这样做
I just...I didn't think they would.
天哪
Jesus.
这就是箭头计划 是不是?
It's the Arrowhead Project, isn't it?
这场雾就是 所谓的军事试验失败的结果?
This mist,it's some kind of,what,military fuckup?
你们这帮家伙究竟在那儿乱搞什么 哼?
What were you guys messin' with up there, huh?
我们捉到你了 你这狗娘养的!
We got you now, you sorry son of a bitch!
进去!
Get in there!
是他们! 这一切都是他们弄出来的!
It was them! It was them what done it to us!
是他们给我们招来了上帝的怒火的
It was them what brung down the final wrath upon us!
一直跟他在一起的
Those two peckerwoods that...
那两个家伙
he's been with this whole time,
之所以在里屋上吊 是因为他们是知道原因的!
they hung themselves in the back because they knew!
他们一直都是知道的!
They knew it all along!
- 他疯的 他不知道...- 跪下!
- He's crazy. He doesn't know...- Get on your knees!
离远点 德雷顿!
Stay out of it, Drayton!
他们也听说过的 不是吗? 你们都知道的!
They heard it too, didn't you? All of ya!
关于箭头计划的一切
All about the Arrowhead Project
在山里搞的见不得人的一切
and all that secret shit up on the mountain.
就是这些让我们落得现在这种地步
That's what brung it down on us.
让主对我们发火
That's what brung down the wrath of God!
二等兵杰斯厄
Private Jessup.
不是我
It wasn't me.
我只是...我只是驻扎在那里
I'm just...I'm stationed up there.
这不是我的责任...
I'm not responsible...
- 胡说! - 冤枉啊 我是本地人!
- Bullshit! - Hell, I'm a local!
你们很多人都认得我的
Most of you people know me.
少装无辜喊冤了
You stop your chicken shit whining
小心我就切掉你的舌头
or I will cut your puling tongue out.
现在你要跟我们坦白!
Now you tell us!
告诉我们
Tell us.
好 好的
Look, look. Okay, okay.
我听说过一些事
I heard stuff.
一些事?
Stuff?
是的 我们都听说过的
Yes, we all heard stuff.
比如他们是怎么样 嗯...
Like how they, um,
他们是怎么样认为存在其他的次元
how they thought that there were other dimensions,
你知道 其他...在我们周围的其他的世界
you know, other...other worlds all around us,
以及他们是怎么样想造一个 嗯...
and how they wanted to try and make, um,
一个窗口...
a window...
你知道 他们就能通过这个窗口
you know, so they could look through...
看另外一个世界是什么样子
and see what's on the other side.
哼 可能你的窗口
Well, maybe your window...
变成一扇门了 是不是?
turned out to be a door. Didn't it?
不是我的! 是那些科学家的!
Not mine! Those scientists'!
啊 是科学家的 对 科学家!
Oh, the scientists! Yes, the scientists!
他们意外地打开了一个洞
They must have ripped a hole open by accident.
这另一个世界的生物便涌到我们这里
This other world came spilling through to ours.
这就是唐纳德逊
That's what Donaldson was saying to me...
自杀前告诉我的
right before he killed himself.
我连一半都听不懂
I didn't understand the half of it.
这不是我的错!
It ain't my fault!
不是 他的 错
Ain't. His. Fault.
不 不 不是的
No, no, no.
什么也不是
Ain't nothin'
谁也没有错
ever anybody's fault.
可是他不承认
But he denies it.
而且又指责别人
He points the finger,
这个藏在我们中间的犹大
this Judas in our midst.
犹大!
Judas!
戴维!
David!
你! 你!
You! You!
你现在还不懂吗?
Don't you know by now?
你还不明白真相吗?
Don't you know the truth?
我们正受到惩罚
We are being punished.
为什么? 因为我们违背了主的旨意!
For what? For going against the will of God!
违背了他古老的禁令!
For going against his forbidden rules of old!
登上月球!
Walking on the moon!
是的! 是的!
Yes! Yes!
- 还...还有搞什么分裂原子! - 阿门!
- Or...or splitting his atoms! - Amen!
还...还有...什么干细胞和堕胎!
Or...or...or stem cells and abortions!
还想探索生命的秘密
And destroying the secrets of life
而这只有主才有权力这样做!
that only God above has any right to!
阿门! 阿门!
Amen! Amen!
是的 我知道! 这是真的!
Yes, I know! It is true!
现在我们正受到惩罚
And now we are being punished.
主对我们的审判已经到来
The judgment is being brought down upon us.
你们看到 地狱里的魔鬼已经被松开
The fiends of hell, you see they are let loose,
并且开始发泄他们的恨意!
and star Wormwood blazes!
这都是他的错!
And it is his fault!
不! 不! 这不是我的错! 不是的!
No! No! It is not my fault! No!
这都是他们做的! 他们亵渎了万能的主
They did it! They spit in the eye of the Almighty!
不是的!
No!
滚回去!
Get over there!
不要这样!
No!
犹大!
Judas!
吉姆!
Jim!
杀了他! 吊死他!
Kill him! String him up!
站起来 你这懦夫!
Stand up, you coward!
老天!
Jesus!
不要
No!
赎罪!
Expiation!
- 不要 - 戳死他!
- No! - Stab him!
赎罪!
Expiation!
扔他出去喂怪物!
Feed him to the beast!
赎罪!
Expiation!
让那些怪兽闻一闻他的血!
Let the abominations smell his blood!
不要 不能这样!
No, no! No!
- 上帝! 等等 - 戴维 不要去!
- Jesus! Wait! - No, David!
求你了
Please.
今晚怪物不会来打扰我们了
The beast will leave us alone tonight.
明天...
Tomorrow...
明天 我们等着瞧吧
tomorrow, we'll just have to wait and see.
爸爸
Daddy.
对不起 把你丢下了 孩子
Sorry I left you, pal.
我再也不会丢下你了
I'll never leave you again.
保证吗?
Promise?
你一定要向我保证 好吗?
But you have to give me your best promise, okay?
你最重的承诺 永远也不能食言
Your very best promise, and can never break it.
说吧
Tell me.
保证你不会让怪物捉走我
Promise you won't let the monsters get me.
永远 不管什么
Ever. No matter what.
我保证
I promise.
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, Daddy.
我爱你 比利
I love you, Billy.
胜于一切
More than anything.
天要亮了
It's dawn.
嘿 小伙子 准备好回家了吗?
Hey, pal, you ready to go home?
来
Come on.
好了 我把食物藏在
Okay, I got the groceries hidden...
2号收银台里
at check stand number two.
有5袋 我们拿了然后出门
Five bags. We can grab 'em and get out the door.
好
Okay.
我的车停在停车场
My car's parked in the center...
中央车道的远端
lane of the parking lot, far end.
不管谁先到那里 都要把两扇门打开
Whoever gets there first, open up both doors,
然后我们尽快地挤进去 明白吗?
and we'll all pile in as fast as we can, okay?
走吧
Let's go.
要偷食物吗?
Stealing food now?
我们现在要出去 卡莫迪夫人
Going out now, Mrs. Carmody.
请站开
Please stand aside.
你们不能出去 我不许
You can't go out. I won't allow it.
不许?
Won't allow it?
这是违背主的意志的
It's against God's will.
你们到现在还不明白吗?
Don't you know that by now?
我不是一而再 再而三地 证明了我自己了吗?
Haven't I proven myself again and again and again?
你们还不相信我就是他的信使吗?
Haven't I shown that I am his vessel?
你们怎么回事呀?
What's the matter with you?
难道你们不相信主吗?
Don't you believe in God?
没人妨碍你相信主
No one's interfered with you.
我们要的只是同等的权利
All we're asking for is the same privilege.
你们听到了
You heard him.
就是这些人让我们陷入现在这种境地
It is these people who brought this upon us.
就是他们...
They...
这帮人不愿臣服于主的意志
people who refused to bend to the will of God,
还把它说成是特权
and claim it privilege.
一帮傲慢的罪人
Sinners in pride.
对 傲慢
Yes, haughty.
有特权
Privileged!
他们嘲弄了我们 他们嘲弄了我们的主 我们的信仰
They mock us. They mock our God, our faith,
我们的的价值 我们的生活方式
our values, our very lifestyle.
他们嘲弄了我们的谦卑和虔诚
They mock our humility and our piousness.
他们亵渎了我们并且还在笑
They piss on us and laugh.
用以祭祀的人类的血
It's from them
必须取自他们
the blood of human sacrifice must come.
赎罪的血...
From them...
- 来呀 - ...应取自他们
- Come on. -...the blood of expiation.
来呀
Come on.
你试试看
You try it.
你他妈的试试看!
Fuckin' try it!
来呀!
Come on!
- 捉住他们 - 我们要那个男孩
- Get 'em! - We want the boy.
- 我们要那个男孩! - 你们后退!
- We want the boy! - You get back!
- 对! - 你们后退!
- Yeah! - You get back!
捉住那个男孩!
The boy!
捉住那个男孩! 捉住他!
Grab that boy! Grab him!
捉住他!
Grab him!
把那小婊子也捉起来!
And get the whore too!
捉住她!
Grab her!
杀了他们! 把他们全给杀了!
Kill 'em! Kill 'em all!
蹲下! 蹲下! 蹲下!
Stay down! Stay down! Stay down!
我...我杀了她
I...I killed her.
谢谢你 奥利
Thank you, Ollie.
我们走吧
Let's go.
把制冰机拉开
Get that ice machine out of the way, please.
你杀了她!
You killed her!
你谋杀了她!
You murdered her!
我不想杀她的 戴夫
I wouldn't have shot her, Dave,
如果有别的办法的话
not if there'd been any other way.
所以我才说谢谢你
That's why I said thank you.
好了
Okay.
好 那...我们走!
Okay, then...let's go!
起来 麦伦!
Get up, Mellon!
来! 我们得快走!
Come on! We gotta go!
我的脚踝!
My ankle!
好 一直往前冲!
Okay. All the way down!
他们在哪?
Where are they?
伯德! 麦伦!
Bud! Mellon!
安布罗斯!
Ambrose!
我想我的脚断了!
I think I broke it!
坚持一下!
Come on! Come on!
我们得走了! 来吧 走!
We gotta go! Come on, come on!
他们走散了!
They're lost!
- 啊 天哪 - 奥利!
- Oh, Jesus. - Ollie!
奥利!
Ollie!
都是惨叫声!
All that screaming!
他们还在外面吗? 能看见我们吗?
Are they out there? Can they see us?
让我...让我进去! 让我进去!
Let me...let me in! Let me in!
我们走吗?
Are we going?
- 不要 - 不
- No. - Yeah.
不! 不要!
No! No!
- 爸爸 - 戴维
- Daddy. - David.
- 戴维 不要 - 爸爸 不要去
- David, no. - Daddy, no.
- 戴维! - 爸爸!
- David! - Daddy!
回车里来!
Get back in the car!
- 爸爸! - 戴维!
- Daddy! - David!
噢 天啊!
Oh, my God!
啊 天啊!
我们得走了
We gotta go.
我跟她说我会修好的
I told her I'd fix it.
前窗...
Frontwindow...
被打破了
broken open.
树
Tree.
我的...
My...
祖父的树
grandfather's tree.
很遗憾 戴维 我真的很遗憾
I'm sorry, David, I'm just so sorry.
我们 嗯...
Let's, uh...
看这些燃油...能走多远?
see how far this...fuel takes us, huh?
说不定我们能走出这迷雾呢
Maybe we'll get clear of the mist.
我们尽力了
We gave it a good shot.
没有人能够否认
Nobody can say we didn't.
嗯
Nope.
确实如此
Nobody can say that.
我们有 呃...
We got, uh...
四发
four.
四发子弹
Four bullets.
可是我们有5个人
But there's five of us.
我会解决的
I'll figure something out.
来呀!
Come on!
来呀 来呀
Come on. Come on.
来呀
Come on.
来呀 来呀!
Come on, come on!
来呀! 来呀!
Come on! Come on!
他们...他们都死了
They're...they're dead.
为什么?
For what?
编剧并执导
弗兰克·德拉邦特
改编自同名中篇小说
斯蒂芬·金
制 作 人
弗兰克·德拉邦特
丽兹·葛洛瑟
执行制片人
鲍伯·韦恩斯坦
哈维·韦恩斯坦
理查德·萨珀斯坦
联合制片
兰迪·里士满
安娜·加杜尼奥
丹妮丝·胡特
摄  影
罗恩·施密特
艺术指导
格雷戈里·梅尔顿
剪  辑
亨特·M·维阿
原创音乐
马克·艾沙姆
服装设计
乔安娜 Ottobre-梅尔顿
造型设计与化妆效果
格里高利·尼克特洛
霍华德伯杰
视觉特效
埃弗雷特·伯勒尔
选角导演
德博拉·阿奎拉
特里西娅·伍德
和 珍史密斯
托马斯·简
马西娅·盖伊·哈登
劳瑞·侯登
安德鲁·布劳尔
托比·琼斯
威廉姆·赛德勒
杰弗瑞·德穆恩
弗兰西斯·斯特恩哈根
艾莉克莎·黛沃洛斯
内森·甘宝
克里斯·欧文
山姆·威特沃
罗伯特 C·treveiler
大卫·詹森
视觉特效制作
美国CafeFX 特效公司
剧终 谢谢观赏